{
    "id": "4326e96e75ee4ce2a7e10e2ff509b903",
    "title": "Reporting Yes Or No Questions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked Raju if he ....................................... present the previous day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "791e6d6db632436a9d288db3587f3c28"
        },
        {
            "question": "James asked me if I ..................................... to a zoo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have ever been",
                "ever went",
                "had ever been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ba2a66214e2448fa8e294c2204d3ef32"
        },
        {
            "question": "The master asked the girl if she .......................................... any difficulty solving the problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "had",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9e829d9401b0491888631cc31cb90704"
        },
        {
            "question": "The lady asked the servant if he ............................................... her letters from the post office.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "collects",
                "collected",
                "has collected",
                "had collected"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "d2368771aabe493b865e49288e88452d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tom asked Ben whether a boy .................................................. a chance to whitewash a fence every day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gets",
                "got",
                "has got"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "247e3584af7241e18dba47754bcadb2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked the boy whether his father ....................................... to the office.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has gone",
                "had gone",
                "went"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94d3e716b3674faaa266bddec4c7c856"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl asked if she ........................................... home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may go",
                "went",
                "might go"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d855a0292579408d975b53046036e8b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of them asked if they ........................................... call the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "37c0a36ca328417997c9a1e4775a92d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Della asked Madam if she .................................... her hair.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bought",
                "will buy",
                "would buy"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8f921c7c547e4137bc5f3f1e5a350893"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man asked the boy if he ........................................... that himself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cannot do",
                "could not do"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9134da03092a4280865ecad9beddf0be"
        }
    ]
}